[{"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I'm from New York", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I moved around a lot", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I went to CMU", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I'm going to CMU now", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I went to school in India", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I'm going to Japan", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "Somewhere in the Caribbean", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "Just to my parents house, nothing special", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I'm not going anywhere this vacation", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "My mother is Alice", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "She's a professor at CMU", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "Wow, out of everyone ever? I don't know", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "My boyfriend", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I'm not married", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "We met in college", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "We randomly started talking in the subway one day", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I usually study at home", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I concentrate best in the library", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I do my best work when I'm surrounded by other people", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "Working in coffee shops is the best", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I went ice skating", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "Nothing. I studied all weekend.", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I just relaxed a lot", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "My 5th grade teacher was my favorite. We're still in touch", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "Professor Peterson was probably my most influential teacher", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I liked my high school English teacher so much", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I went camping in Maine", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "My family traveled to a lake in the mountains", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I live in Pittsburgh", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "My house is in Shadyside", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "Pittsburgh is home for me", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I'm not sure, sorry", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "Downtown, I guess", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "In the stadium", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "Oh, you don't know her", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "Her name is Ember", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I guess my advisor counts as my boss?", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I really like Adele", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I think Adele has a truly amazing voice", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I don't have any enemies", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "That boy who kicked me under the table when I was 10", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "My parents live in New York, but the rest of my family is in Boston", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "They live with me here in Pittsburgh", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I'm from New York", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "They live all over the place", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I went to Dartmouth", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "In New England", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I studied linguistics", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "Well, that's just what was expected of me.", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I'm a software engineer", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I work as a librarian", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I just want to be happy", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I need to make my parents proud", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I grew up in New York", "answer": "I hope to have a successful career and a happy family", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "What do you do for a living", "answer": "I am a student right now", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Where does your family live", "answer": "They live in Taiwan", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "What did you do for fun last weekend", "answer": "I went to play basketball with my friends", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "How did you meet your wife", "answer": "I am not married", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Where do you live", "answer": "I live in Squirrel Hill", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Who was your favorite teacher", "answer": "Alan Black", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Where do you like going to study", "answer": "LTI office", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "What are your goals in life", "answer": "To have a great family", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Who is your favorite singer", "answer": "Jason Mraz", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Where did you go to school", "answer": "Taiwan", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Where are you going for vacation", "answer": "Lots of places in the U.S. ", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Who is you favorite person", "answer": "Stephen Curry", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Where is the hockey game happening tonight", "answer": "I do not know", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Who is your boss", "answer": "I do not have a boss", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i grew up in Alaska", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i went to school in New York", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i went to school just across the street actually", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i'm going to Florida for vacation", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i'm going to be in Mexico", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i'm actually not going anywhere", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "what do you mean", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "my mother is a lawyer", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "my mother's name is Mary", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "my favorite person is my husband Larry", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "don't have one i like too many people", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "oh that's a great story we met on vacation in Hawaii", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i'm not married", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "sorry that's too private", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i like studying on campus", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i like to study at the library", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "my favorite place to study is actually right at home", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "last weekend i went to the Strip District it was great", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i didn't do anything fun", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "my favorite teacher was my fifth grade science teacher", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i didn't like any of my teachers", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i went to a camp in Cape Cod", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i went to a horseback riding camp in New Hampshire", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i live in Pittsburgh", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "that's a secret", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i don't know anything about a hockey game sorry", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "what hockey game", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i think it's in the Penguins stadium in the North Side", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "my boss is that guy over there", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i'm my own boss", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "my favorite would have to be JLo", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i don't listen to music very often so i don't have an answer", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i love everyone", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "can't tell you", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "that's very private why do you ask", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "my family lives in California", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "my family lives overseas", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i've lost touch with them so i'm not sure", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i didn't attend college", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i haven't gone to college yet i'm only applying this year", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i went to Harvard University", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "because it was the logical next thing to do", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "because i need a college degree to become a lawyer", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i didn't go to college", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i'm a nurse", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i'm a software engineer", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i'm currently unemployed", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "don't have any", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i want to become CEO of a company by age 30", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "i want to retire by age 40", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "04/19/2015 08:53:39,", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "I grew up in Taiwan", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "Taiwan", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "Lots of places in the U.S.", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "Rachel Hong", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "Stephen Curry", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "I am not married", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "LTI office", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "I went to play basketball with my friends", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "Alan Black", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "I did not go for camp last summer", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "I live in Squirrel Hill", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "I do not know", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "I do not have a boss", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "Jason Mraz", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "They live in Taiwan", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "I wen to college in Taiwan", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "To get higher education", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "I am a student right now", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i grew up right around here", "answer": "To have a great family", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Who is your mother", "answer": "Rachel Hong", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Why did you go to college", "answer": "To get higher education", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Where did you go to college", "answer": "I wen to college in Taiwan", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Where did you go for camp last summer", "answer": "I did not go for camp last summer", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Where did you grow up", "answer": "I grew up in Taiwan", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}]